Guide to the Louis H. Pollak Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Supreme Court Justices files, 1989-2012; Series IV
  This series includes correspondence with and other documents relating to several current and former justices of the United States Supreme Court.
  Conditions Governing Access
  Correspondence with any current or former Justice of the United States Supreme Court shall remain closed to all research until the death of that Justice or former Justice.
  - Alito, Samuel, 2005 (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - Breyer, Stephen G., Associate Justice, 2000-2010 (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - Ginsburg, Ruth Bader, 1993-2011 (Box 60, Folder 3-4)
  - Kagan, Elena (Supreme Court Justice; Dean, Harvard), 2008, 2010 (Box 60, Folder 5)
  - Kennedy, Anthony, 2008, 2012 (Box 60, Folder 6)
  - O'Connor, Sandra Day, 2001-2005 (Box 60, Folder 7)
  - Sandra Day O'Connor Project on the State of the Judiciary
    - Fair and Independent Courts: A Conference on the State of the Judiciary, 2006
    - Our Courts and Corporate Citizenship, 2008 Conference
    - Striking the Balance: Fair and Independent Courts in a New Era, 2009 Conference
      - Invitation, registration, program, 2009 (Box 60, Folder 8)
      - Recording
  - Scalia, Antonin, 1989-2000 (Box 60, Folder 9)
  - Souter, David H., 1997-2012 (Box 60, Folder 10-11)
  - Stevens, John Paul, Associate Judge, 2000-2012 (Box 60, Folder 12)
  - Thomas, Clarence, 2010 (Box 60, Folder 13)
- Computer files (Box 61–64)
  Original born digital files, as well as preservation masters, may not be accessed due to their fragility. Researchers must consult use copies, or if none exist request that they be made. Born digital files cannot be accessed remotely. System requirements include a Manuscripts and Archives computer and file viewing software.